ordertiger.com 2019-06-29

# Systems Privacy Policy - Order Tiger

This Policy applies as between you, the user (“User”) of this website (“Web Site”) and/or mobile application (“Application”) and Order Tiger (“Us” or “We”) and the company (“Branded Company”) whose branding is displayed on the Web Site and/or Application that links to this Privacy Policy respects the privacy of use of our Web Site, Applications and online services (“Services).  
This Policy applies to our use of any and all data (“Data”) collected by us in relation to your use of the Web Site, Applications and any Services or Systems therein while providing such Data to users on behalf of the Branded Company. This privacy policy does not apply to any Web Sites, Applications or other Services that do not link to this policy.

## 1\. DEFINITIONS AND INTERPRETATION

In this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings:

"Account"  
means collectively the personal information, Payment Information and credentials used by Users to access Material and/or any communications System on the Web Site and Applications;  
"Content"  
means any text, graphics, images, audio, video, software, data compilations and any other form of information capable of being stored in a computer that appears on or forms part of this Web Site and Applications;  
"Cookie"  
means a small text file placed on your computer by Order Tiger when you visit certain parts of this Web Site. This allows us to identify recurring visitors and to analyze their browsing habits within the Web Site. Further details are contained in Clause 9 of this Policy;  
"Data"  
means collectively all information that you submit to the Web Site and Applications. This includes, but is not limited to, Account details and information submitted using any of our Services or Systems;  
"Order Tiger”  
mean this Web Site and Applications is owned and operated by Order Tiger Limited. And it is an intellectual and confidentiality property of Order Tiger Limited.  
"Services”  
means collectively any online facilities, tools, services or information that Order Tiger makes available through the Web Site and Applications either now or in the future;  
"System"  
means any online communications infrastructure thatOrder Tiger makes available through the Web Site and Applications either now or in the future. This includes, but is not limited to, web-based email, message boards, live chat facilities and email links;  
"User"/"Users"  
means any third party that accesses the Web Site and Applications and is not employed by Order Tiger and acting in the course of their employment. A third party who avails services from Order Tiger or just visit the website for any type of information.  
"Web Site"  
means the Branded Company website that you are currently using unless expressly excluded by their own terms and conditions.  
“Applications”  
means the Branded Company iOS and Android mobile application that you are currently using unless expressly excluded by their own terms and conditions.  
“Branded Company”  
when you order menu items from the branded company Web Site and Applications we will  
send your order to the Branded Company location choose by you, so that the Branded Company can fulfil your order.  
We may also share your personal information with the Branded Company or their Third Party Providers so that they can directly market their products and services to you.

## 2\. DATA COLLECTED

Without limitation, any of the following Data may be collected:

2.1 name;  
2.2 title;  
2.3 gender;  
2.4 address such as street address, area, postcode and city.  
2.5 contact information such as email addresses and telephone numbers;  
2.6 financial information such as credit / debit card numbers;  
2.7 web browser type and version (automatically collected);  
2.8 operating system (automatically collected);  
2.9 a list of URLS starting with a referring site, your activity on this Web Site, and the site you exit to (automatically collected);  
2.10 Cookie information (see clause 9 below).

## 3\. OUR USE OF DATA

3.1 Any personal Data you submit will be retained by Order Tiger for as long as you use the Services and Systems provided on the Web Site and Applications. Data that you may submit through any communications System that we may provide may be retained for a longer period of up to twelve months.  
3.2 Unless we are obliged or permitted by law to do so, and subject to Clause 4, your Data will not be disclosed to third parties. This does not include our affiliates and/or other companies within our group.  
3.3 Any or all of the above Data may be required by us from time to time in order to provide you with the best possible service and experience when using our Web Site and Applications. Specifically, Data may be used by us for the following reasons:  
3.3.1 internal record keeping;  
3.3.2 improvement of our products/services;  
3.3.3 transmission by email of promotional materials that may be of interest to you;  
3.3.4 Contact for market research purposes which may be done using email, telephone, fax or mail. Such information may be used to customize or update the Web Site and Applications.

## 4\. THIRD PARTY WEB SITES AND SERVICES

Order Tiger may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with matters that may include, but are not limited to, payment handling, search engine facilities, advertising and marketing. The providers of such services do not have access to certain personal Data provided by Users of this Web Site and Applications. Furthermore, any Data that is processed by third parties must be processed within the terms of this Policy.

## 5\. CHANGES OF BUSINESS OWNERSHIP AND CONTROL

5.1 Order Tiger may, from time to time, expand or reduce its business and this may involve the sale of certain divisions or the transfer of control of certain divisions to other parties. Data provided by Users will, where it is relevant to any division so transferred, be transferred along with that division and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this Policy, be permitted to use the Data for the purposes for which it was supplied by you.  
5.2 In the event that any Data submitted by Users will be transferred in such a manner, you will not be contacted in advance and informed of the changes.

## 6\. YOUR RIGHT TO WITHHOLD INFORMATION

6.1 You may access certain areas of the Web Site and Apps without providing any Data at all. However, to use all Services and Systems available on the Web Site and Applications you may be required to submit Account information or other Data.  
6.2 You may restrict your internet browser´s use of Cookies. For more information see clause 9.4 below.

## 7\. ACCESSING YOUR OWN DATA

7.1 You may access your Account at any time to view or amend the Data. You may need to modify or update your Data if your circumstances change. Additional Data as to your marketing preferences may also be stored and you may change this at any time.  
7.2 You have the right to ask for a copy of your personal Data on payment of a small fee.

## 8\. SECURITY

Data security is of great importance to Order Tiger and to protect you’re Data we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure Data collected online.

## 9\. COOKIES

9.1 Order Tiger may set and access Cookies on your computer.  
9.2 A Cookie is a small file that resides on your computer´s hard drive and often contains an anonymous unique identifier and is accessible only by the web site that placed it there, not any other sites.  
9.3 You may delete Cookies; however, you may lose any information that enables you to access the Web Site more quickly.  
9.4 You can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your web browser. By default, your browser will accept Cookies, however, this can be altered. For further details please consult the help menu in your browser. Disabling Cookies may prevent you from using the full range of Services available on the Web Site.

9.5 By visiting our web site third parties (such as AdRoll) may place cookies on users’ browsers for targeted advertising purposes.

9.6 Your IP addresses, cookie identifiers and website activity are collected for targeted advertising.

9.7 This data may be used by third parties (such as AdRoll) to target advertising on other sites based on your users’ online activity.

9.8 To opt out of receiving targeted advertising visit following link: [youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

9.9  _  Cookies may also be used to track how you use and interact with the website to target ads to you on other websites._

## 10\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Order Tiger reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy as we may deem necessary from time to time or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on the Web Site and you are deemed to have accepted the terms of the Policy on your first use of the Web Site following the alterations.
